ojooo.com 2017-10-03

# Ojooo.com - Privacy policy

## This privacy policy covers Ojooo AG and group companies and our websites, products and services.

 **Websites:**

_Please read this privacy policy carefully. By accessing and using our websites, products and services you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy. You must not register with us or sign up to any of our Services if you do not accept this privacy policy._

Our principal activity is to provide telecommunications software, applications, systems, solutions, products and services ("Services").

In this privacy policy, "we" "us" and "our" mean Ojooo AG and group companies and "you" and "your" means the person accessing our websites and Services.

This privacy policy provides you with details about the personal information we collect from you, how we use your personal information and your rights to control personal information we hold about you.

We are committed to the privacy of our customers and will only process personal information you provide to us in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. This policy explains how we collect personal information and the uses to which we put this personal information. This policy also provides details of the security measures we take to safeguard your personal information and your privacy.

**Collection and Use**

When you contract with us or otherwise contact us regarding any of our Services, the information you provide to us will be stored and used to help in the process of providing our Services. Such information includes names, postal addresses, telephone numbers, email addresses, credit and debit card details and is used for such purposes as:

  * Provisioning of our Services
  * Identifying customers when they contact us with a query
  * Customer support
  * Maintaining call records
  * Identifying customer preferences so that we can give recommendations about other products and services offered by us and our carefully selected business partners that may be of interest
  * Customer registration and administration
  * Billing and account administration
  * Credit checking
  * Administration and management of our business systems
  * Technical and operational administration
  * Security requirements
  * Complying with legal and regulatory requirements
  * As otherwise required or permitted by law

We may disclose information to:

  * third parties involved in the development, promotion, marketing or enhancement of our Services
  * third parties for administrative purposes (such as billing, support, marketing, etc.)
  * third parties for the provision of their products or services to our customers
  * other third parties upon receiving your consent or as required by law

To download and install our OJOOO APP App you have to provide us with your phone number so that we can access your mobile device's address book. A copy of the phone numbers and names in your mobile device's address book is kept on our servers and is used by us for the following purposes:

  * to notify you when any of your contacts download and install the OJOOO APP
  * to show contacts who are OJOOO APP users
  * to display contact names when you receive a call via the OJOOO APP

Your details may need to be passed to other service providers in order for us to provide our Services to you.

We may disclose information to third parties that we retain to analyse aggregated anonymous statistical information about your use of our Services.

Personal information may also be disclosed in connection with a sale, transfer or reorganisation of any of our businesses, in which case we will require that personal information will continue to be treated in accordance with this privacy policy or as otherwise permitted by law.

We collect personal information that you volunteer while using our Services. We do not collect or use personal information for any purpose other than that indicated in this privacy policy. Should we wish to use your personal information for a new purpose, we shall first contact you and seek your consent to this new purpose.

We may share your personal information with other companies in the Ojooo AG group or with other carefully selected organisations with which we have a trusted business relationship. We may we use your personal information to provide you with promotional information about new and other products and services offered by us and organisations with whom we have a trusted business relationship. At any time, if you do not wish to continue receiving promotional information of this type, you may notify us at https://ojooo.com/contact.php whereupon we shall stop sending promotional information to you.

We will not sell or rent your personal information to any third party unless you have consented to this. If you do consent but later change your mind, you may contact us at https://ojooo.com/contact.php and we will stop any such activity.

**Confidentiality and Security**

We take all reasonable care to keep your personal information confidential and to prevent any unauthorised access to your personal information. The security of your information is very important to us. We have implemented security measures to protect the personal information that we have under our control from:

  * Unauthorised access
  * Improper use or disclosure
  * Unauthorised modification
  * Unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of personal information belonging to our customers, suppliers, partners and visitors.

Whilst we take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard the personal information that you provide to us, no transmission over the Internet and communication network can ever be guaranteed to be secure. As such, we cannot guarantee the security of any personal information that you transfer electronically to us.

We are not responsible for any actual, indirect or consequential damages (or any other damages or liability of any kind whatsoever, whether as a result of negligence or otherwise) that may result from a lapse in compliance with this privacy policy arising from a security breach or technical malfunction.

**Cookies**

We use cookies on our websites. A cookie is a file that is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use the following types of cookie:

Session Cookies

Session Cookies are temporary and will be deleted from your computer when you leave our websites.

Persistent Cookies

Persistent Cookies remain on your computer until they are deleted by you or they expire.

Cookies are used to track and maintain continuity of web sessions such as the process of signing up to our Services. Cookies also enable us track visitors and allow you to look back at earlier registration pages and improve our Services.

The Cookies we use do not collect personal information about you other than the IP address from which you are accessing our websites.

You can set your Internet web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to prevent cookies from being sent or to search for and delete cookies stored on your computer. If you prevent a cookie from being sent or if you delete a cookie, you may reduce the functionality of our websites. For more information on disabling cookies please visit www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies or visit your Internet web browser's help menus.

**Third Party Websites**

Our privacy policy applies only to the personal information that we collect and we cannot be responsible for personal information that third parties may collect, store and use through their websites, products and services. Our Services and websites may include links to third party websites, products and services. We do not represent or warrant that any information or material that may be obtained through any link from us is accurate, complete or current. We do not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage that may arise as a result of relying upon such information or material. Information and material contained in any third party website, products and services is outside our control and will be subject to third party intellectual property rights, separate terms of use and policies covering data use and privacy. You are strongly recommended to read applicable terms and policies before using any third party website, products or services.

**Overseas Disclosures**

Personal information held by us is stored and processed in the Germany, the European Economic Area and the US.

**Policy Changes**

We may change this privacy policy either due to business reasons or changes in legislation. We shall update the "Last modified" date in the event of any change.

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children.

**Access to the personal information we may hold about you**

If you want to know what personal information we are holding on you then you can ask us at https://ojooo.com/contact.php

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal information which we keep about you within a week but we may require proof of your identity before disclosing personal information. We reserve our right to charge an administration fee to cover our costs in providing such information to you.

We reserve the right to refuse to provide a copy of your personal information, but will give reasons for our refusal.

Reading and accepting this agreement you allow us to contact you via email.

**Partnership Program.**

Every customer can use free OJOOO APP - A free of charge, but he can also participate in the Partnership Program, which will reward him for further products' recommendation.

Products starting from OJOOO messenger may vary and new ones can appear as well. 

For each product registered, Partnership Program participants will receive to choose from tangible products from our catalogue, or the equivalent of $ 5 in cash, by bank transfer to an account, only through our payment systems, after deducting the costs of the transfer. Prices of products and their value can change.

Each partner in the program is obliged to pay all the taxes by himself in accordance with his national law.

**Enquiries**

If you have an enquiry about our privacy policy, please contact us at <https://ojooo.com/contact.php>

Last modified date: 5th May 2016.
